MATTEO GREGORICCHIO

Date of Birth21/10/1992Addresscorso Casale 210, Torino - 10132Phone+39 338 661 3822Emailmatteo.gregoricchio@mail.com
matteo.gregoricchio@libero.itPersonal Sitewww.matteogregoricchio.comLinkedinhttps://it.linkedin.com/in/matteo-
gregoricchio



Upwork http://www.upwork.com/o/profiles/users/_~01ca9d34312f7fa73d/

I'm an **Art History Graduate**. During my studies I worked as a **freelancer translator** on the platform Upwork. Currently I'm studying the fundamental technologies (HTML, CSS, Javascript and Jquery, Ruby on Rails) to become a **full-stack developer**.

My best **traits & skills** are synthesis, precision and work organization. I'm an order passionate, I'm independent and I'm really resolute: if I have a task, I don't stop until I've completed it! You can find proof on my Upwork profile, where you'll see how I've always completed on time my contracts with max rating.

My main **interests** are contemporary art (with a focus on Latin America production), videogames, literature, the IT field (especially web programming) and the World Wide Web. Lastly, I'm a football fan!

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance Translator at Techpump S.L.

05/2015 - 05/2018

Translation projects eng-ita, online cultural contents.

Internship at Polo Museale del Piemonte, Torino (TO)

11/2016 - 12/2016

Internship for Master's Degree. Employee at Education and Services Office. 150 hours.

➢ Freelance Translator at WebInterpret

02/2015 - 11/2015

Translation/adaptation to italian of englistings for e-commerce platforms.

> Traineeship at Technical Office, Moruzzo (UD)

03/2014 - 05/2014

Archive catalogation at Technical Office, Moruzzo (UD). Stage part of Bachelor's Degree program.250 hours.

EDUCATION

Master's Degree, Art History

2015 - 2017, Università degli Studi di Torino [Final Grade: 110 e Lode/110] Dissertation: *Il conceptualismo ideológico nell'Argentina degli anni '70: analisi dell'operato del Grupo CAYC;* supervisors: José Luis de la Nuez Santana, Franca Varallo; topics: latinamerican contemporary art, contemporary argentine art ('60-'70 of the 20th century).

Bachelor's Degree, Conservation of Cultural Assets 2011 - 2015, Università degli Studi di Udine [Final Grade: 108/110] Dissertation: *Julio Castellanos e i Contemporáneos;* supervisor: Mario Sartor; topics: latinamerican contemporary art, contemporary mexican art ('20-'40 of the 20th century).

Secondary School Diploma

2006 – 2011, I.S.I.S. Vincenzo Manzini, San Daniele del Friuli (UD)

LANGUAGE COMPETENCE

► Italian: Mother Tongue

English: Professional KnowledgeSpanish: Professional Knowledge

IT COMPETENCE

- **ECDL Certificate** n. IT 1049910, released from AICA on 25/01/2007.
- **Advanced** Knowledge of **Windows** and **Apple Systems**.
- ≥ Advanced Knowledge of Microsoft **Office** and **LibreOffice** suites.
- **Advanced** Knowledge of **web surfing** and **web searching** and **e-mail systems**.
- ≥ Good Knowledge of **HTML** & **CSS**.
- ≥ Basic Knowledge of **Javascript & jQuery**.

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

COURSES

> Full-Stack Developer Career on Lacerba.io

01/2018 - today

on course 6/7 (jQuery). The career focuses on those programming languages:

1-4. HTML & CSS 5-6. Javascript & jQuery 7. Ruby on Rails.

[List and courses syllabus is on: http://lacerba.io/p/full-stack]

In compliance with the Italian legislative Decree no. 196 dated 30/06/2003, I hereby authorize you to use and process my personal details contained in this document.

Turin, 05/2018